=My Rich Little Brother=
= أخي الغني الصغير =
=Episode 11=
= الحلقة 11 =
Yingying,
ينجينج ،
you shouldn't have to handle such heavy work, right?
لا يجب عليك تحمل مثل هذا العمل الشاق ، أليس كذلك؟
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
Quite right!
حق تماما!
Have a seat, Yingying.
اجلس يا ينجين.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Have some fruit.
تناول بعض الفاكهة.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Why am I being replaced?
لماذا يتم استبدالي؟
I don't care who the new boss is.
لا يهمني من هو الرئيس الجديد.
I won't accept this.
لن أقبل هذا.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
It's you.
انه انت.
It's been a while.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
They say we have a new leader here.
يقولون لدينا قائد جديد هنا.
The beauty of our sales department
جمال قسم المبيعات لدينا
wants to invite you out for dinner.
يريد دعوتك لتناول العشاء.
What about lunch? We can go together.
ماذا عن الغداء؟  يمكننا الذهاب معا.
Zhengzheng,
Zhengzheng ،
guess who I saw today at work?
خمن من رأيته اليوم في العمل؟
Your older brother.
أخوك الأكبر.
It's been two years
لقد مر عامان
and he seems even more mature.
ويبدو أنه أكثر نضجًا.
Is this the surprise you talked about?
هل هذه هي المفاجأة التي تحدثت عنها؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
What's wrong with your head?
ما خطب رأسك؟
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
I'm done with all the work
لقد انتهيت من كل العمل
purchasing this company.
شراء هذه الشركة.
It's just that Dad asked me
لقد سألني أبي فقط
to run it personally.
لتشغيله شخصيًا.
Didn't you agree to let me do it?
ألم توافق على السماح لي بفعل ذلك؟
I never saw you being so keen
أنا لم أرَك أبدًا حريصًا جدًا
on running a part of the business.
في إدارة جزء من العمل.
Could it be
هل من الممكن ذلك
there's another reason?
هناك سبب آخر؟
Mr. Wei is really handsome.
السيد وي حقا وسيم.
And this restaurant is pretty nice.
وهذا المطعم جميل جدا.
Miss Wei,
ملكة جمال وي ،
to congratulate you on your promotion,
لتهنئتك على الترقية ،
let's raise our coffee cups
دعونا نرفع فناجين القهوة لدينا
to toast your success.
لتحميص نجاحك.
Mr. Wei,
السيد وي ،
I happened to be wondering if we could talk about this.
تصادف أنني أتساءل عما إذا كان بإمكاننا التحدث عن هذا.
With my current work experience,
مع خبرتي العملية الحالية ،
I am not qualified to be a manager.
أنا لست مؤهلاً لأكون مديرًا.
So
لذا
I think it would be better
أعتقد أنه سيكون أفضل
for me to take my time
بالنسبة لي لأخذ وقتي
and work my way up slowly.
وأعمل طريقي ببطء.
That's fine.
هذا جيّد.
Let's put business aside.
دعونا نضع العمل جانبًا.
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng.
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
Take a seat.
اجلس.
How's your injury?
كيف حال إصابتك؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Why didn't you
لماذا لم تفعل
ask me out to this meal?
اسألني للخروج لهذه الوجبة؟
I'd like to touch up my makeup.
أود أن أضبط مكياجي.
Mr. Wei,
السيد وي ،
where is the bathroom?
أين الحمام؟
Just down the hall.
فقط أسفل القاعة.
I still don't know where.
ما زلت لا أعرف أين.
Why don't you show me the way?
لماذا لا تريني الطريق؟
Do you remember this place?
هل تتذكر هذا المكان؟
Wow.
رائع.
It's still the same.
لا يزال على حاله.
Tomorrow.
الغد.
Tomorrow I'll officially confess my love to you.
غدا سأعترف لك رسميا بحبي.
I won't be your little brother anymore.
لن أكون أخوك الصغير بعد الآن.
I want to be your official boyfriend.
اريد ان اكون صديقك الرسمي.
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
♪ أنا قلق إذا شعرت بالتوتر ♪
(Next episode) I'm not a kid anymore.
(الحلقة التالية) لم أعد طفلاً.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You're not a kid anymore.
لم تعد طفلاً.
Then,
ثم،
let's do something
دعنا نفعل شيئا ما
that adults do.
الذي يفعله الكبار.
- You...
- أنت ... - أنت ...
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
♪We can't let go♪
♪ لا يمكننا تركه ♪